[
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 1?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 1",
      "javascript option B 1",
      "javascript option C 1",
      "javascript option D 1"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 1",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 1."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 2?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 2",
      "javascript option B 2",
      "javascript option C 2",
      "javascript option D 2"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 2",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 2."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 3?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 3",
      "javascript option B 3",
      "javascript option C 3",
      "javascript option D 3"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 3",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 3."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 4?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 4",
      "javascript option B 4",
      "javascript option C 4",
      "javascript option D 4"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 4",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 4."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 5?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 5",
      "javascript option B 5",
      "javascript option C 5",
      "javascript option D 5"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 5",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 5."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 6?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 6",
      "javascript option B 6",
      "javascript option C 6",
      "javascript option D 6"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 6",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 6."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 7?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 7",
      "javascript option B 7",
      "javascript option C 7",
      "javascript option D 7"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 7",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 7."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 8?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 8",
      "javascript option B 8",
      "javascript option C 8",
      "javascript option D 8"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 8",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 8."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 9?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 9",
      "javascript option B 9",
      "javascript option C 9",
      "javascript option D 9"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 9",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 10?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 10",
      "javascript option B 10",
      "javascript option C 10",
      "javascript option D 10"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 10",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 10."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 11?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 11",
      "javascript option B 11",
      "javascript option C 11",
      "javascript option D 11"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 11",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 11."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 12?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 12",
      "javascript option B 12",
      "javascript option C 12",
      "javascript option D 12"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 12",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 12."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 13?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 13",
      "javascript option B 13",
      "javascript option C 13",
      "javascript option D 13"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 13",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 13."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 14?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 14",
      "javascript option B 14",
      "javascript option C 14",
      "javascript option D 14"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 14",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 14."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 15?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 15",
      "javascript option B 15",
      "javascript option C 15",
      "javascript option D 15"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 15",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 15."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 16?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 16",
      "javascript option B 16",
      "javascript option C 16",
      "javascript option D 16"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 16",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 16."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 17?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 17",
      "javascript option B 17",
      "javascript option C 17",
      "javascript option D 17"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 17",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 17."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 18?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 18",
      "javascript option B 18",
      "javascript option C 18",
      "javascript option D 18"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 18",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 18."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 19?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 19",
      "javascript option B 19",
      "javascript option C 19",
      "javascript option D 19"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 19",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 19."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 20?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 20",
      "javascript option B 20",
      "javascript option C 20",
      "javascript option D 20"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 20",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 20."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 21?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 21",
      "javascript option B 21",
      "javascript option C 21",
      "javascript option D 21"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 21",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 21."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 22?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 22",
      "javascript option B 22",
      "javascript option C 22",
      "javascript option D 22"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 22",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 22."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 23?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 23",
      "javascript option B 23",
      "javascript option C 23",
      "javascript option D 23"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 23",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 23."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 24?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 24",
      "javascript option B 24",
      "javascript option C 24",
      "javascript option D 24"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 24",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 24."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 25?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 25",
      "javascript option B 25",
      "javascript option C 25",
      "javascript option D 25"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 25",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 25."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 26?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 26",
      "javascript option B 26",
      "javascript option C 26",
      "javascript option D 26"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 26",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 26."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 27?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 27",
      "javascript option B 27",
      "javascript option C 27",
      "javascript option D 27"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 27",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 27."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 28?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 28",
      "javascript option B 28",
      "javascript option C 28",
      "javascript option D 28"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 28",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 28."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 29?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 29",
      "javascript option B 29",
      "javascript option C 29",
      "javascript option D 29"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 29",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 29."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 30?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 30",
      "javascript option B 30",
      "javascript option C 30",
      "javascript option D 30"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 30",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 30."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 31?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 31",
      "javascript option B 31",
      "javascript option C 31",
      "javascript option D 31"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 31",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 31."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 32?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 32",
      "javascript option B 32",
      "javascript option C 32",
      "javascript option D 32"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 32",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 32."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 33?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 33",
      "javascript option B 33",
      "javascript option C 33",
      "javascript option D 33"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 33",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 33."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 34?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 34",
      "javascript option B 34",
      "javascript option C 34",
      "javascript option D 34"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 34",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 34."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 35?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 35",
      "javascript option B 35",
      "javascript option C 35",
      "javascript option D 35"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 35",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 35."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 36?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 36",
      "javascript option B 36",
      "javascript option C 36",
      "javascript option D 36"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 36",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 36."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 37?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 37",
      "javascript option B 37",
      "javascript option C 37",
      "javascript option D 37"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 37",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 37."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 38?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 38",
      "javascript option B 38",
      "javascript option C 38",
      "javascript option D 38"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 38",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 38."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 39?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 39",
      "javascript option B 39",
      "javascript option C 39",
      "javascript option D 39"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 39",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 39."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 40?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 40",
      "javascript option B 40",
      "javascript option C 40",
      "javascript option D 40"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 40",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 40."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 41?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 41",
      "javascript option B 41",
      "javascript option C 41",
      "javascript option D 41"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 41",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 41."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 42?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 42",
      "javascript option B 42",
      "javascript option C 42",
      "javascript option D 42"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 42",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 42."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 43?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 43",
      "javascript option B 43",
      "javascript option C 43",
      "javascript option D 43"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 43",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 43."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 44?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 44",
      "javascript option B 44",
      "javascript option C 44",
      "javascript option D 44"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 44",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 44."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 45?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 45",
      "javascript option B 45",
      "javascript option C 45",
      "javascript option D 45"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 45",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 45."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 46?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 46",
      "javascript option B 46",
      "javascript option C 46",
      "javascript option D 46"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 46",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 46."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 47?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 47",
      "javascript option B 47",
      "javascript option C 47",
      "javascript option D 47"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 47",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 47."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 48?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 48",
      "javascript option B 48",
      "javascript option C 48",
      "javascript option D 48"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 48",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 48."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 49?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 49",
      "javascript option B 49",
      "javascript option C 49",
      "javascript option D 49"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 49",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 49."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 50?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 50",
      "javascript option B 50",
      "javascript option C 50",
      "javascript option D 50"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 50",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 50."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 51?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 51",
      "javascript option B 51",
      "javascript option C 51",
      "javascript option D 51"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 51",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 51."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 52?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 52",
      "javascript option B 52",
      "javascript option C 52",
      "javascript option D 52"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 52",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 52."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 53?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 53",
      "javascript option B 53",
      "javascript option C 53",
      "javascript option D 53"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 53",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 53."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 54?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 54",
      "javascript option B 54",
      "javascript option C 54",
      "javascript option D 54"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 54",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 54."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 55?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 55",
      "javascript option B 55",
      "javascript option C 55",
      "javascript option D 55"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 55",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 55."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 56?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 56",
      "javascript option B 56",
      "javascript option C 56",
      "javascript option D 56"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 56",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 56."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 57?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 57",
      "javascript option B 57",
      "javascript option C 57",
      "javascript option D 57"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 57",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 57."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 58?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 58",
      "javascript option B 58",
      "javascript option C 58",
      "javascript option D 58"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 58",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 58."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 59?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 59",
      "javascript option B 59",
      "javascript option C 59",
      "javascript option D 59"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 59",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 59."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 60?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 60",
      "javascript option B 60",
      "javascript option C 60",
      "javascript option D 60"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 60",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 60."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 61?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 61",
      "javascript option B 61",
      "javascript option C 61",
      "javascript option D 61"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 61",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 61."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 62?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 62",
      "javascript option B 62",
      "javascript option C 62",
      "javascript option D 62"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 62",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 62."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 63?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 63",
      "javascript option B 63",
      "javascript option C 63",
      "javascript option D 63"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 63",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 63."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 64?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 64",
      "javascript option B 64",
      "javascript option C 64",
      "javascript option D 64"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 64",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 64."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 65?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 65",
      "javascript option B 65",
      "javascript option C 65",
      "javascript option D 65"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 65",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 65."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 66?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 66",
      "javascript option B 66",
      "javascript option C 66",
      "javascript option D 66"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 66",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 66."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 67?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 67",
      "javascript option B 67",
      "javascript option C 67",
      "javascript option D 67"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 67",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 67."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 68?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 68",
      "javascript option B 68",
      "javascript option C 68",
      "javascript option D 68"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 68",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 68."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 69?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 69",
      "javascript option B 69",
      "javascript option C 69",
      "javascript option D 69"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 69",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 69."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 70?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 70",
      "javascript option B 70",
      "javascript option C 70",
      "javascript option D 70"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 70",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 70."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 71?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 71",
      "javascript option B 71",
      "javascript option C 71",
      "javascript option D 71"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 71",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 71."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 72?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 72",
      "javascript option B 72",
      "javascript option C 72",
      "javascript option D 72"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 72",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 72."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 73?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 73",
      "javascript option B 73",
      "javascript option C 73",
      "javascript option D 73"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 73",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 73."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 74?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 74",
      "javascript option B 74",
      "javascript option C 74",
      "javascript option D 74"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 74",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 74."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 75?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 75",
      "javascript option B 75",
      "javascript option C 75",
      "javascript option D 75"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 75",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 75."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 76?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 76",
      "javascript option B 76",
      "javascript option C 76",
      "javascript option D 76"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 76",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 76."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 77?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 77",
      "javascript option B 77",
      "javascript option C 77",
      "javascript option D 77"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 77",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 77."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 78?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 78",
      "javascript option B 78",
      "javascript option C 78",
      "javascript option D 78"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 78",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 78."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 79?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 79",
      "javascript option B 79",
      "javascript option C 79",
      "javascript option D 79"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 79",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 79."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 80?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 80",
      "javascript option B 80",
      "javascript option C 80",
      "javascript option D 80"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 80",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 80."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 81?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 81",
      "javascript option B 81",
      "javascript option C 81",
      "javascript option D 81"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 81",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 81."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 82?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 82",
      "javascript option B 82",
      "javascript option C 82",
      "javascript option D 82"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 82",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 82."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 83?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 83",
      "javascript option B 83",
      "javascript option C 83",
      "javascript option D 83"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 83",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 83."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 84?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 84",
      "javascript option B 84",
      "javascript option C 84",
      "javascript option D 84"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 84",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 84."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 85?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 85",
      "javascript option B 85",
      "javascript option C 85",
      "javascript option D 85"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 85",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 85."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 86?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 86",
      "javascript option B 86",
      "javascript option C 86",
      "javascript option D 86"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 86",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 86."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 87?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 87",
      "javascript option B 87",
      "javascript option C 87",
      "javascript option D 87"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 87",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 87."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 88?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 88",
      "javascript option B 88",
      "javascript option C 88",
      "javascript option D 88"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 88",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 88."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 89?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 89",
      "javascript option B 89",
      "javascript option C 89",
      "javascript option D 89"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 89",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 89."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 90?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 90",
      "javascript option B 90",
      "javascript option C 90",
      "javascript option D 90"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 90",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 90."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 91?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 91",
      "javascript option B 91",
      "javascript option C 91",
      "javascript option D 91"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 91",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 91."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 92?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 92",
      "javascript option B 92",
      "javascript option C 92",
      "javascript option D 92"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 92",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 92."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 93?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 93",
      "javascript option B 93",
      "javascript option C 93",
      "javascript option D 93"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 93",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 93."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 94?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 94",
      "javascript option B 94",
      "javascript option C 94",
      "javascript option D 94"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 94",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 94."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 95?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 95",
      "javascript option B 95",
      "javascript option C 95",
      "javascript option D 95"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 95",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 95."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 96?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 96",
      "javascript option B 96",
      "javascript option C 96",
      "javascript option D 96"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 96",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 96."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 97?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 97",
      "javascript option B 97",
      "javascript option C 97",
      "javascript option D 97"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 97",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 97."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 98?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 98",
      "javascript option B 98",
      "javascript option C 98",
      "javascript option D 98"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 98",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 98."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 99?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 99",
      "javascript option B 99",
      "javascript option C 99",
      "javascript option D 99"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 99",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 99."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JAVASCRIPT concept 100?",
    "options": [
      "javascript option A 100",
      "javascript option B 100",
      "javascript option C 100",
      "javascript option D 100"
    ],
    "answer": "javascript option A 100",
    "explanation": "This is explanation for JAVASCRIPT concept 100."
  }
]